smileybux.com 2017-11-12

# Privacy Policy | TexasHoldEm.com

TexasHoldEm.com is committed to maintaining the trust and confidence of its Players and visitors to its Website. We are also committed to the security of the data we collect. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to enable you to understand when we collect and use information about you, the actions we take to protect your privacy and our commitment to data security.   This Privacy Policy should be read in conjunction with the Terms and Conditions located on the Website. Periodically we may make changes to this Privacy Policy that will include changes to this page. It is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy frequently and remain informed about any changes to it. We encourage you to visit this page regularly.

**1\. Information Collected  
**  
When you visit TexasHoldEm.com there are two types of information that you may provide us with: (a) personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and (b) website use information that is collected as you and others browse our Website. In general, you can visit our Website at www.TexasHoldEm.com without revealing any personal information about yourself. (a) Personal Information Personal Information is any information that may be used to identify an individual, including but not limited to first & last name, contact details including mailing address, email address and phone numbers and credit card information (“Personal Information”). If you are only browsing the Website you will not be asked to provide any Personal Information. If you choose to download the TexasHoldEm.com client and open a  Free Player account, you will need to provide us with Personal Information. We do not collect Personal Information about you at TexasHoldEm.com unless you voluntarily provide it to us. (b) Website Information When you interact with our Website, our servers keep an activity log unique to you that collects certain information including: IP address, time and date of access, web pages visited and type of browser used. This is not considered Personal Information. The Website uses your IP address to administer our Website, diagnose problems with our server, track activity within our Website and collect demographic data. The demographic data we collect is used to enhance features on our Website. IP addresses may also be used by TexasHoldEm.com to prevent and investigate collusion.

**2\. How Do We Use Your Information?  
**  
We use the Personal Information you provide us for the purpose of administering our business and providing customer support.  This may entail disclosure to any company within the TexasHoldEm.com group of companies and their employees who have a need to know such information, as well as any potential purchasers or investors in any company within the TexasHoldEm.com group of companies. Your Personal Information may also be shared with our affiliates, subsidiaries or agents for technical support and to process the transactions you initiate on the Website. It may also be provided to any third parties which provide services to TexasHoldEm.com in order for us to provide you with services, including by way of example payment processors, data verifiers, and auditors Occasionally, we may use the Personal Information you’ve given us to notify you about important changes to our Website, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. You will be given the opportunity to notify us of your desire not to receive these offers by clicking on an unsubscribe link when you receive an offer. We may also, from time to time, request information from you via surveys or contests. Participation in any survey or contest is entirely voluntary and you have the choice of whether or not to take part. By accepting any contest prize or winnings from TexasHoldEm.com, you consent to the use of your name and likeness for advertising and promotional purposes without additional compensation, except where prohibited by law. TexasHoldEm.com will not sell or share your Personal Information except as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

**3\. Security  
**  
While connected to the Website, privacy of all information exchanges is protected using the international standard SSLv3/TLSv1. This security system uses encrypted algorithms to ensure that your Personal Information remains private. Along with your name, credit card numbers and passwords, game play information also passes through this encryption.

**4\. Legal Disclosure  
**  
We may disclose your Personal Information if requested to do so by legal authorities, if required to do so by law, or if we believe in good faith that such action is required to (a) conform to the applicable laws or to comply with any legal process served on us; (b) protect or defend our rights or property; or (c) act to protect the personal safety of the public.

**5\. Opting Out  
**  
You may opt out of receiving any promotional communication from TexasHoldEm.com by choosing to opt out where such option is made available on the Website or in an email you receive from us or at any time by emailing us at [support@TexasHoldEm.com](mailto:privacy@tropicalpoker.com). In addition you may email us at any time to request a copy of the Personal Information you have given us, to confirm the accuracy of the Personal Information we have collected about you, to update your Personal Information or if have a concern about the use of your Personal Information.  We may  levy a small charge to cover the cost of administration

**6\. Cookies  
**  
Cookies are small text files that are stored on your computer when you visit certain web pages that record your preferences. The Website uses cookies to track usage of the Website and to compile statistical data on your use of our Website. We also may use cookies to improve the Website. Most web browsers allow you to restrict or allow the use of cookies. You are not obligated to accept the cookie from the Website however, if you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to enjoy all of the interactive features the Website offers.

**7\. Protection of Children  
**  
The Website and its products are not intended for or directed to persons under the age of 18.  We do not knowingly collect any Personal Information from children.  Any person who provides their Personal Information to us represents to us that they are 18 years of age or older. It is our policy to adhere to the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act and to use our best efforts to comply with that Act. To read the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act visit: http://www.ftc.gov/ogc/coppa1.htm

**8\. Third Party Coverage  
**  
This Privacy Policy applies to the Website. We cannot ensure the protection of any information or images that your provide to a third party web site that links to or from the Website or any information collected by any third party administering our affiliate program or any other program as these third party web sites are owned and operated independently of TexasHoldEm.com.

**9\. International Transfers  
**  
Personal Information collected by TexasHoldEm.com may be stored and processed in any country in which we, our subsidiaries or our affiliates maintains facilities and by using the Website and software you consent to any transfer of Personal Information outside of your home country.

**10\. Retention  
**  
Your Personal Information will not be stored for any longer period than is necessary for the purposes for which it was collected.

**11\. Legal Disclaimer  
**  
TexasHoldEm.com operates on an “As Is” basis, without liability of any kind. We are not responsible for events beyond our control. Due to the complexity and constantly changing nature of the Internet, technology and our business we cannot fully guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration of data will not occur. TexasHoldEm.com is not liable for any indirect, incidental, consequential or punitive damages relating to the use or release of Personal Information.

**12\. Consent to the Privacy Policy  
**  
By creating an account at TexasHoldEm.com, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Web site and software constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any updates. Visit this page frequently to view the most recent version of TexasHoldEm.com’s Privacy Policy. TexasHoldEm.com Privacy Policy last updated:  August 2011
